Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personal papers, 1860-1992; MS2027 Series 4
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0431-0440, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0441-0450, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0451-0460, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0461-0470, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0471-0480, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0481-0490, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0491-0500, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0501-0510, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0511-0520, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0521-0530, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0531-0540, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0541-0550, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0551-0560, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0561-0570, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0571-0580, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0581-0590, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0591-0600, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 38, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0601-0610, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0611-0620, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0621-0630, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0631-0640, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0641-0650, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0651-0661, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0662-0673, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0674-0687, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0688-0701, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0702-0716, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0717-0729, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0730-0740, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0741-0750, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0751-0760, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0761-0770, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0771-0780, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0781-0790, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0791-0800, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0801-0810, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0811-0820, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 39, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0821-0830, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0831-0840, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0841-0850, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0851-0860, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0861-0870, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-#0871-0876, nd, undated (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#767-775, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#776-795, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#796-815, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#816-834, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#835-854, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#855-874, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#875-893, 1971-1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#894-909, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#910-928, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#929-950, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#951-968, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#969-985, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#986-1003, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#1004-121 item 1, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 40, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#1022-1040, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#1041-1059, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#1060-1079, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#1080-1096, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series II-#196 item 1-1105, Series IIA-#1006-114 item 1, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#114 item 2-1033, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1034-1050, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1051-1068, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1069-1086, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1087-1104, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1105-1124, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1125-1146, 1972-1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1147-1163, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1164-1183, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1184-1202, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1203-1222, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1223-1240, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1241-1260, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1261-1278, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1279-1298, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 41, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1299-1318, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1319-1336, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1337-1354, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1355-1374, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1375-1393, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#1394-149 item 3, 1973-1974 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series IIA-#149 item 4-1428, 1974 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#01-20, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#21-38, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#39-57, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#58-75, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#76-93, 1970 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#94-106, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#107-126, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#127-146, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#147-166, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#167-184, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#185-203, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#204-219, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#220-236, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 42, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#237-256, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#257-275, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#276-295, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#296-313, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#314-332, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#333-350, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#350-363, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#364-377, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#378-397, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#398-419, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#418-431, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#432-451, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#452-471, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#472-491, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#492-510, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#511-529, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#530-545, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#546-561, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#562-586, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#581-600, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 43, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#601-618, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#619-637, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#638-652, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 3)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#653-670, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 4)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#671-689/, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 5)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#690-706, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 6)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#707-725, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 7)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#726-745, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 8)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#746-762, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 9)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#762.1-780, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 10)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#781-798, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 11)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#799-810, 819-824, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 12)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#825-841, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 13)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#842-860, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 14)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#861-877, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 15)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#878-897, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 16)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#898-916, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 17)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#917-936, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 18)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#937-955, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 19)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#956-974, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 44, Folder 20)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#975-994, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 45, Folder 1)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#995-18 item 4, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 45, Folder 2)
  - William J. Stephenson files: Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Slides-Series III-#1009-1012, 1976 (Box SHARED Box 13, Box 45, Folder 3)
- Records of past presidents Ken Rollins, Rachael Stewart and Carl Linden, 1954-2013; Series 5; 10 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains articles, photographs, correspondence, statements, pamphlets, brochures, maps, reports, cassettes, videocassettes, DVDs, and slides that were acquired during the association presidencies of Ken Rollins, Carl Linden, and Rachel Stewart.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Association, May 5, 2014 (2014.013)
  - Possible illege tree-cutting within Park with letter and 7 pages with photos and drawings, 2007; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Written by donor, "sent by Level Walker Carl Pederson to Carl Linden detailing possible illegal cutting of trees between Four Locks and McCoy's Ferry
  - Contact information containing C&O Canal Association address and email lists for Board of Directors, membership lists, and lists of Park service personnel, 1995-2010; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Presidents of the C&O Canal Association, 1957-2001; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Undated document from James R. Preston to the C&O Canal Association listing all of the Association's presidents from 1957 to 2001 and listing "The Immortal Nine" who went on the 1954 Justice Douglas walk. Copy of Jim Preston's 1998 Toast to the Association's Presidents. Undated letter from James R. Preston to Association members titled "Facts and information on our association's beginnings." Assorted Association lists and general information about the newsletter.
  - 2002 Draft Land Protection Plan Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Historical Park (spiral bound copy), 2002-2003; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Written by donor "authored by William J. Spinrad, Jr. and copy of letter from the US Department of Interior to interested parties inviting public comment."
  - Topographic map of Great Falls area, 2001 January 06; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - 20th Anniversary Reunion Hike: 2 copies of yellow covered pamphlet with copies of photos and newspaper articles and list of participants, 1974 April 17-24; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Geological Survey Bulletin 2123: Geology of the Harpers Ferry Quadrangle, Virginia, Maryland and West Virginia, 1996; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Special Projects committee: several loose sheets, 2003-2004; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Nomination form for C&O Canal National Register of Historic Places: 2 copies, 1979; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - 45th Douglas Hike, with color photo of participants, participants list, and schedule, 1999; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - C&O Canal Memories by Lavenia Waskey, reprinted for the 50th Anniversary of the Douglas Hike, 2004; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Along the Towpath: 2 issues, and The Canaller: 1 issue, 1986 January-April-1998; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Potomac River Water Trail maps, 2002 April; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - C&O Canal Maps, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Liability discussions: notes, emails, correspondence, 2002-2003; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Through Hike: containing newspaper articles and photos, 1999; Series 5 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - 3 Canal Flood Recovery studies, 1977-1997; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    "We are again in the midst of trouble": flooding on the Potomac River and the Struggle for the Sustainability of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal, 1928-1996 by Donald R. Shaffer (July 1977) C&O Canal National Historical Park Flood Recovery Action Plan--draft in progress dates 3/15/97 C&O Canal National Historical Park Flood Recovery Plan, revised December 1997
  - Conococheague Aqueduct: paper from Brent H. Carter, USBR Diving Officer and Regional Geologist on Underwater Examination, Conococheague Creek Aqueduct, 1994-1995; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Big Slackwater: Towpath/Detour Options for Big Slackwater, Final Report., 1998 December 12; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Written by donor " Revised December 12, 1998. Prepared for the National Park Service by Dewberry & Davis, Fairfax VA."
  - Big Slackwater: Rehabilitate, Reconstruct and Stabilize Big Slackwater Historic Stone Wall and Towpath, 2009 November; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    Written by donor, "-PMIS 60110 Environmental Assessment/Assessment of Effect"
  - 40th Anniversary Thru Hike poem: "The door to the towpath opened" composed by James R. Preston, 1994; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Flood coverage: copies of newspaper articles and photographs, 1996 January-February; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Board meeting notes--misc notes and handouts, 2003; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Topographic maps of Pawpaw Tunnel area, 1999; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - 50th Anniversary Through Hike, 2004; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Special Projects Committee backup material, 2008-2009; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Trolley Barn-new exhibits, 2008; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - 1976 Cactoctin Aqueduct: Historic Structure Report by Harlan D. Unrau, Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Board meeting notes, 2007 June; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Widewater: Environmental Assessment Rehabilitation of Historic Towpath & Retaining Wall at Widewater, 2003 June; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - A Collection of Maps of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal, 1967; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    Written by donor, "3rd edition, published by Potomac Area American Youth Hostels Inc"
  - Centennial Observer and C&O Chronicle, v1 #6, 1962 May; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Brookmont: "Brookmont Unremembered Days" by Grant Conway, 1972 October; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Flood recovery efforts, 1996 January; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 18)